<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>5.2.0</latestVersion>
    <url>https://github.com/steve1316/uma-android-automation/releases</url>
    <releaseNotes>
v5.2.0 - Changelog

New
---
- Add a new option to the `Settings` page to set a date to stop the app at.
- Add new options to the `Debug Settings` page to enable the `Remote Log Viewer`. This allows users to view the logs from their browser on separate devices in real-time. Requires both devices to be on the same Wi-Fi network to work.
- The drawer now has the app icon in it as well as a footer with a pressable link to the GitHub repo.
- Add a checkbox to the `Skill Plan Settings` pages to filter out the unselected skills.
- Add logic to determine whether an in-game button is disabled or not.
- Add `Team Carrot` as an option in the `Training Event Settings` page for Unity Cup Team Selection.
- Add a new option in the `Debug Settings` page to start a OCR detection test for the trainee's name from the aptitude dialog.
- Add missing options in the `Debug Settings` page for the `Main Screen` and `Training Screen` tests.
- Add edge case handling of artificial boost of side-effect gains for Guts training.
- Add more selection reasons at the end of training analysis.
- Log trainings that needed corrections at the end of training analysis with asterisks.
- Add more edge case handling for the training stat gain corrections.

Adjustments
---
- Update the game data up to Admire Vega 2026-03-04.
- Update `Automation Library` version to 2.5.0.
- Adjust the starting Discord message that is sent to display the link to the `Remote Log Viewer` as clickable when it is enabled.
- Curb the output of loading log messages.
- Adjust the conditions of when the smart racing plan is checked so it races more often.
- Set the smart racing parameters to new default values so it races more often.
- Image asset cleanup and use them as components instead.
- Shorten the scroll distance when scrolling down as skills are being scanned when purchasing skills.
- Log the leftover skill points after skill plan execution.
- Log all skills scanned when purchasing skills.
- Always enforce Wit training on the final turn 75.

Fixed
---
- Fix bugs related to scrolling lists.
- Fix rare bug that causes infinite loops due to the app running too fast.
- Fix regression where running style was not being reset anymore after Junior Year.
- Fix bug where the app is unable to send the final Discord message when the run ends due to it finishing too fast.
- Fix several edge cases involving the Race Preparation screen.
- Fix bug where SQLite settings were not syncing.
- Fix bug where the app goes too fast and miss clicking on the Skills button at Career End.
- Fix using the wrong mapping to check for side-effect stat gains during training analysis.
- Fix require cycle involving the `SkillPlanSettings.tsx` and `BotStateContext.tsx`.
    </releaseNotes>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>